benchmarks are very important to
computer manufacturers so usually there
are standards organizations that put
together benchmark suites for use in
comparing performance between machines
so usually there is a benchmarking
organization that takes input from
manufacturers of systems from user
groups from experts in academia and so
on and produces a standard benchmark
suite along with instructions on how to
produce representative measurements so
this is how we got tpc
benchmarks
which are used for databases web servers
data mining and other transaction
processing so-called embassy benchmarks
which are used in embedded processing
such as cars video players printers
phones etc so if we're testing a
processor for for example potentially
using a car
we would use the embassy benchmarks not
the tpc
and the spec benchmarks which are
typically used to evaluate engineering
workstations and also raw processors
because these benchmarks unlike the
other two
are not very i o intensive they're
mostly
processor oriented
so the spec benchmark suite includes a
number of applications such as gcc
which represents software development
workloads like a compiler
several applications like b waves and
lbm that are representative of fluid
dynamics workloads perl
which is representative of string
processing applications catus adm this
is a physics simulation related to
relativity this is a parser for xml
several solvers of differential
equations
b zip a compression application two game
ai applications and so on as you can see
the spec benchmarks really try to cover
a variety of potential uses for
processors and high performance systems